== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Sheldon:)Yeah-- there's hooks in the
closet, I can hang it right now.
(Penny:)Oh, no, no,
Th-those hooks are gone.
(Sheldon:)What happened to them?
(Penny:)Uh, we ran out of candy
on Halloween,
(Penny:)I was just giving
everything away.
Hey, guys, what are you...?
(Leonard:)Oh, that's here, cool.
(Penny:)Amy wants me to have it.
(Amy:)Well, it would be selfish
of me to keep it.
B-But it's a picture of you.
(Amy:)And you.
(Penny:)But you commissioned it.
(Amy:)To give to you.
(Penny:)But you like it so much.
(Amy:)So do you.
(Penny:)I seem to be losing.
(Leonard:)Yes, you do.
(Sheldon:)You know, Leonard,
the more I think about it,
(Sheldon:)there are a number of mutually
owned items in this apartment
(Sheldon:)that you and I
should go through.
(Sheldon:)Uh, for example...
(Sheldon:)who gets our beloved sword,
Longclaw?
(Penny:)Why don't you keep it?
That seems fair;
we did just give you
(Sheldon:)the painting.